powerbalance.com 2017-12-29

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy covers how **POWER BALANCE** treats Personal Information (as defined in the Terms of Use) that **POWER BALANCE**  collects and receives on the Website, including information related to your past use of the Website. Your Personal information is information about you that may or may not be personally identifiable like your user name, password, email address, or personal profile data that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that **POWER BALANCE**  does not own or control or to people that **POWER BALANCE**  does not employ or manage. All Personal Information containing your email and any answers solicited from you for a Profile that is entered into the Website by you is private to you except to the extent that you opt – against our recommendation - to share such Personal Information with other members. Other than for the reasons explicitly described below, it is the policy of **POWER BALANCE**  not to disclose Personal Information to any third party at any time.

Conversely, given that a portion of the purpose of the Website is to share what its customers have experienced with others, our policy regarding Submissions is very different. While our objective is to safeguard your identity, privacy and anonymity, our goal is also to publicly publish and promote the Submissions that describe what you have experienced without identifying who you are so that others can recognize experiences that have been shared by people who are similar in background to themselves. Always use caution when giving out any personally identifiable information about yourself, other family members or friends in the Website. **POWER BALANCE**  does not control or endorse the content, messages or information exchanged by means of the Website and, therefore, **POWER BALANCE**  specifically disclaims any liability with regard to the Website and any actions resulting from your participation in the Website.

**POWER BALANCE**  collects Personal Information when you register with, use or visit the Website, and when you visit the pages of certain **POWER BALANCE**  partners. **POWER BALANCE**  may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your user name, password, email address, and personal profile. Once you register with **POWER BALANCE**  and sign in to the Website you may not be completely anonymous to us. **POWER BALANCE**  may collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. **POWER BALANCE**  may set and access cookies on your computer.

  * **POWER BALANCE**  may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, **POWER BALANCE**  cookie information, and the pages you request.
  * **POWER BALANCE**  may use information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide reporting for internal and external clients.
  * **POWER BALANCE**  does not rent, sell, or share your Personal Information with third parties except to provide products or services you've previously requested, or unless we have your express permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with **POWER BALANCE**  under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your Personal Information to help communicate with you about news and information related to **POWER BALANCE**. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of **POWER BALANCE's** Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We transfer information about you if **POWER BALANCE**  is acquired by or merged with another company. 

**California Residents:**   
Your California Privacy Rights Under California law, our Members customers that are California residents may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As detailed above, we do not share our customer's personal information with unaffiliated third parties for direct marketing purposes without their approval.

If at any time you wish to opt out of having your personal information shared with third parties and or receiving information from **POWER BALANCE**  (via e-mail or postal mail) about new products, services, or promotions, you can do so. You may contact us at by e-mailing us at [opt-out@powerbalance.com](mailto:opt-out@powerbalance.com). Please indicate what publications or services you no longer wish to receive so that we may better address your needs.

Your personally identifiable information is one of our most valuable assets. It is kept physically secure in our data centers and is accessible only to authorized personnel as needed to perform operations governed by this policy. In addition, when **POWER BALANCE**  collects information from you, **POWER BALANCE**  uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, the industry standard for protecting privacy in web transactions. Please keep in mind that despite these measures, **POWER BALANCE**  cannot guarantee or warrant 100% security of its servers and databases. Moreover, **POWER BALANCE**  cannot guarantee that personally identifiable information that you submit through the Website will not be intercepted.

**POWER BALANCE**  believes that it is especially important to protect children's privacy online. **POWER BALANCE**  does not knowingly collect or use any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 and **POWER BALANCE**  does not knowingly provide any personally identifiable information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever from visitors younger than 13 years old. No information should be submitted to or posted at **POWER BALANCE**  by visitors younger than 13 years old.

Any inquiries concerning this Privacy Policy should be directed to [info@powerbalance.net](mailto:info@powerbalance.net).
